

Payam Zahedi FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Accomplished Frontend Developer with over 8 years of experience in software development, including 5 years focused on Flutter and Dart for mobile and embedded applications. Recently expanded expertise to include Astro and Open Harmony, demonstrating adaptability and a passion for emerging technologies. Actively engaged in the open-source community as the main maintainer for tools such as Flutter Toastification and snapp_cli, and recognized for leadership through event organization and conference speaking.

payamzahedi95@gmail.com

Berlin, Germany

payam-zahedi

(in) payamzahedi95

WORK EXPERIENCE

• Sep 2024 - **Present** Senior Software Engineer, Snapp Mobile, Germany Remote

• Sep 2022 - **Present** Senior Software Engineer, Snapp X, Germany

• Jul 2021 - Sep 2022 Senior Flutter Developer, REKAB Technologies, Turkey Remote

• Jun 2020 - Jul 2021 Flutter Developer, Ra Secret Project, Remote

• Jun 2019 - May 2020 Flutter Developer, Dropp Technologies Group, Iran

PROJECTS

• **Estimate Me**: An Al-driven project cost estimation tool with a custom web interface and optimized Al models.

• Flutter Toastification: Toastification is a Flutter package for displaying customizable toast messages.

• **snapp_cli**: Dart CLI for Easily set up and remote debug Flutter apps on Raspberry Pi and other devices.

• **fl_chart**: I'm a contributor to the fl-chart package, a versatile and highly customizable chart library for Flutter.

• Fantom: an Open API generator designed for Dart and Flutter, developed using Pure Dart.

• For more open source projects, checkout My GitHub

TALKS AND CONFERENCES

• Persian Flutter: Al for Developers | Online - 2024

• Flutter and Friends: Beyond Mobile: Powering Embedded Devices with Flutter | Stockholm - 2024

• Fluttercon Berlin: Flutter-Powered Candy Dispenser on Raspberry Pi 5 | Berlin - 2024

• Persian Flutter: Flutter Embedded Overview | Online - 2024

• Berlin Meetup: Flutter's journey on Embedded world - 2024

SKILLS

• Flutter: Expert

• **Embedded**: Advanced

• Android: Good

• iOS: Normal

Astro: Advanced

• Python: Good

Riverpod, Bloc, MobX ...

• MVVM, TDD, Clean

• gRPC, REST, socket

• Isar, Hive, Sqfentity

• GitHub Actions, Azure, Code • Active Learning

magic

Firebase: Vertex AI, Firestore

dart cli

• Embedded flutter: flutter-pi,

ivi homescreen

EDUCATIONAL

• Master of Software engineering Gorgan Azad University | 2017 - 2019

 Bachelor of Software engineering Gorgan Azad University | 2013 - 2017

WORK EXPERIENCE IN DETAIL



Senior Software Engineer Remote, Germany | Sep 2024 - Present

Both <u>SnappX</u> and <u>Snapp Mobile</u> are part of the same parent company, <u>Snapp Holding</u>. For a specific period, I was temporarily transferred to the Snapp Mobile team to assist with particular projects, contributing my skills to support their initiatives during that time.

- Researched OpenHarmony for mobile app development potential.
- Developed **oh-app-action (Github Action)** to automate OpenHarmony setup in CI/CD pipelines.
- Created multiple pipelines in azure DevOps system.
- Developed a Soundcloud clone OHOS app with REST API integration and local database support.
- audio streaming via media playback and utilized the Open Harmony Distributed Data Object API.



Senior Software Engineer Remote, Germany | Sep 2022 - Present

Snapp X is an agency dedicated to bringing **Flutter** to any **screen**. In addition to **mobile** app development, we specialize in **embedded** projects and have created developer tools to simplify embedded application development.

- Collaborated with Flutter custom embedders (flutter-pi, ivi-homescreen, flutter-elinux).
- Streamline Flutter installation on embedded Linux devices using <u>snapp_installer</u> (a bash script).
- Contributed to **snapp_cli**: a Dart CLI tool enabling **remote debugging** on embedded devices.
- Interface with sensors, motors, and actuators through Flutter applications.



Senior Flutter Developer Remote, Turkey | Jul 2021 - Sep 2022

<u>Rekab City</u> is a multi-module trip planner platform. You can easily plan your trip with public transport and get live updates about network interruptions.

- Worked on multimodule (packages without dependencies) architecture.
- Struct Architecture based on MobX and Freezed in flutter.
- Worked with **Mapbox** as the main map of the app.
- Created a completely customized design system.
- · Worked with background services.



Flutter Developer

Iran, Gorgan | Jun 2019 - May 2020

Dropp Technologies is a company Which develops Mobile and Web applications. I have worked on several applications in Dropp and learned various concepts.

- Struct an architecture base on Bloc and Equatable.
- Construct chat part with **socket.io** to increase the speed in comparison with Firebase.
- Work with animations and transitions in flutter.
- Experienced Google map package and Google services.

ARTICLES

- · Articles written in English
- Articles written in Persian

VOLUNTARY EXPERIENCE



Co-Founder

Jul 2021 - Present

LANGUAGE

- English (Fluent)
- German (A1)
- Persian (Native)